<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TOP GLOBAL COMPANIES</string>


    <string-array name="comName">
        <item>ICBC</item>
        <item>JPMorgan Chase</item>
        <item>China Construction Bank</item>
        <item>Agricultural Bank of China</item>
        <item>Bank of America</item>
        <item>Apple</item>
        <item>Ping An Insurance Group</item>
        <item>Bank of China</item>
        <item>Royal Dutch Shell</item>
        <item>Wells Fargo</item>
        <item>ExxonMobil</item>
        <item>AT&amp;T</item>
        <item>Samsung Electronics</item>
        <item>Citigroup</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="comCoun">
        <item>China</item>
        <item>United States</item>
        <item>China</item>
        <item>China</item>
        <item>United States</item>
        <item>United States</item>
        <item>China</item>
        <item>China</item>
        <item>Netherlands</item>
        <item>United States</item>
        <item>United States</item>
        <item>United States</item>
        <item>South Korea</item>
        <item>United States</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="comIndus">
        <item>Major Banks</item>
        <item>Major Banks</item>
        <item>Major Banks</item>
        <item>Regional Banks</item>
        <item>Major Banks</item>
        <item>Computer Hardware</item>
        <item>Diversified Insurance</item>
        <item>Major Banks</item>
        <item>Oil and Gas Operations</item>
        <item>Major Banks</item>
        <item>Oil and Gas Operations</item>
        <item>Telecommunications services</item>
        <item>Semiconductors</item>
        <item>Major Banks</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="comCEO">
        <item>Shu Gu</item>
        <item>Jamie Dimon</item>
        <item>Wang Zuji</item>
        <item>Huan Zhao</item>
        <item>Brian T. Moynihan</item>
        <item>Tim Cook</item>
        <item>Ma Mingzhe</item>
        <item>Chen Siqing</item>
        <item>Bernardus Cornelis Margriet van Beurden</item>
        <item>Timothy Allen Sloan</item>
        <item>Darren W. W. Woods</item>
        <item>Randall L. L. Stephenson</item>
        <item>Hyun-Suk Kim</item>
        <item>Michael L. Louis Corbat</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="comInfo">
        <item>Industrial and Commercial Bank of China Ltd. engages in the provision of commercial banking and financial services. It operates through the following business segments: Corporate Banking, Personal Banking, Treasury Operations, and Others. The Corporate Banking segment offers corporate loans, trade financing, deposit-taking and custody activities, corporate wealth management, and corporate intermediary services. </item>
        <item>JPMorgan Chase and Co. is a financial holding company, which provides financial and investment banking services. It offers a range of investment banking products and services in all major capital markets, including advising on corporate strategy and structure; capital-raising in equity and debt markets; sophisticated risk management; market-making in cash securities and derivative instruments; and prime brokerage and research.</item>
        <item>China Construction Bank Corp. engages in the provision of financial and banking services. It operates through the following segments: Corporate Banking, Personal Banking, Treasury Business, and Others. The Corporate Banking segment includes credit businesses, institutional business services, fund settlement and custody, and corporate e-banking.</item>
        <item>Agricultural Bank of China engages in the provision of international commercial banking and financial services. The company operates its business through the following segments: Corporate Banking, Personal Banking, Treasury Operations and Others and Unallocated. The Corporate Banking segment provides financial products and services to corporations, government agencies and financial institutions.</item>
        <item>Bank of America Corp. is a bank and financial holding company, which engages in the provision of banking and nonbank financial services. It operates through the following segments: Consumer Banking, Global Wealth and Investment Management, Global Banking, Global Markets, and Legacy Assets and Servicing. The Consumer Banking segment offers credit, banking, and investment products and services to consumers and small businesses.</item>
        <item>Apple, Inc. engages in the design, manufacture, and marketing of mobile communication, media devices, personal computers, and portable digital music players. It operates through the following geographical segments: Americas, Europe, Greater China, Japan, and Rest of Asia Pacific. The Americas segment includes both North and South America. </item>
        <item>Ping An Insurance (Group) Co. of China Ltd. engages in the provision of financial products and services. The company primarily engages in the business of insurance, banking and investment. Its activities also include investment in financial and insurance enterprises and investment deployment. The company operates through the following segments: Life Insurance, Property and Casualty, Banking, Securities and Corporate.</item>
        <item>Bank of China Ltd. engages in the provision of banking and related financial services such as commercial and investment banking, and insurance and investment services. The company operates its business through the following segments: Corporate Banking, Personal Banking, Treasury Operations, Investment Banking, Insurance, and Others</item>
        <item>Royal Dutch Shell Plc engages in the oil and natural gas production. It operates through three segments: Upstream, Downstream, and Corporate. The Upstream segment combines the operating segments Upstream International and Upstream Americas, which are engaged in exploring for and recovering crude oil and natural gas; the liquefaction and transportation of gas; the extraction of bitumen from oil sands that is converted into synthetic crude oil; and wind energy.</item>
        <item>Wells Fargo and Co. is a bank holding company that engages in the provision of banking, insurance, investments, mortgage, and consumer and commercial finance. It operates through the following segments: Community Banking, Wholesale Banking, and Wealth and Investment Management.</item>
        <item>Exxon Mobil Corp. engages in the exploration, development, and distribution of oil, gas, and petroleum products. It operates through the following segments: Upstream, Downstream, and Chemical. The Upstream segment produces crude oil and natural gas. </item>
        <item>AT&amp;T, Inc. is a holding company, which engages in the provision of telecommunications and digital entertainment services. It operates through the following segments: Business Solutions, Entertainment Group, Consumer Mobility, and International. The Business Solutions segment includes wired and wireless services to customers who purchased through employer-sponsored plans.</item>
        <item>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. engages in the manufacturing and selling of electronics and computer peripherals. The company operates its business through following business divisions: Consumer Electronics, Information Technology and Mobile Communications and Device Solutions. The Consumer Electronics business division provides cable television, monitor, printer, air-conditioners, refrigerators, washing machines, and medical devices. </item>
        <item>Citigroup, Inc. is a global financial services holding company specializes in banking and financial solutions. It offers a range of products and services among individuals, corporations, governments and institutions such as savings, checking, online banking, individual retirements accounts, credit cards; personal, student, and commercial real estate loans, cash management services, home equity, and bill consolidation, as well as online banking services, cash management, transactions, trade, securities, and fund services. </item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
